On your Windows Open command prompt.
I'm on Mac. I'll open the terminal.
If you have installed A-W-S-C-L-S successfully,
you should see this window.
Type a W SEN version on Windows.
It may show different on Mac. It shows this.
Next, you'll type AWS configure.
Now open the access key file
that you have on your downloads folder.
So I have my own open here.
I'm gonna copy the access key Id. Select this.
Right click copy. Right click paste. Here, enter. Next.
I'm gonna paste the access key.
I'll grab the access key from the file.
Again, select this right click.
Copy right here. Paste it. Enter.
Very important. Choose US East one.
No matter where you're in the world, choose US East one.
This is critical for our hands-on.
To go smoothly, choose US east one only always
for our hands-on, and then click on enter again.
Click enter. We have now configured A-W-S-C-L-I on our
system.